{
    "id": "15be93913f804c6bb1edc9af9430abe7",
    "title": "Figures Of Speech Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Let him be rich and weary.",
            "description": "Paradox is a statement that seems absurd or self-contradictory but may actually be true.",
            "answers": [
                "Paradox",
                "Oxymoron",
                "Hyperbole"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "37f13a670c944d589f74ff63162e05fe"
        },
        {
            "question": "So innocent arch, so cunningly simple.",
            "description": "When two contradictory qualities of the same thing are mentioned at once, it is called oxymoron.",
            "answers": [
                "Antithesis",
                "Oxymoron",
                "metaphor"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "31fef36e90e34ba2ac55bad1f0f6228f"
        },
        {
            "question": "All the perfumes of Arabia will not sweeten this little hand.",
            "description": "When a statement is made emphatic by overstatement, it is called hyperbole.",
            "answers": [
                "Hyperbole",
                "Oxymoron",
                "Antithesis"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ef1bd6fe260b4f68be57d7448afdc1c9"
        },
        {
            "question": "All the world is a stage.",
            "description": "A metaphor is an implied simile. It makes an indirect comparison.",
            "answers": [
                "Metaphor",
                "Paradox"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "5252e9d10532404e9f2a847f6be14246"
        },
        {
            "question": "The mountains sing together, the hills rejoice and clap hands.",
            "description": "When inanimate objects are spoken of as having life, it becomes personification.",
            "answers": [
                "Antithesis",
                "Personification",
                "Metaphor"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ce62e6c5ff92459493533b1930df230a"
        },
        {
            "question": "Many are called, but few are chosen.",
            "description": "When opposite ideas are placed side by side for emphasis it is called antithesis.",
            "answers": [
                "Antithesis",
                "Euphemism",
                "Personification"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "df7ac661f3cb47198130997f9a80047d"
        },
        {
            "question": "Men may come and men may go, but I go on for ever.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Oxymoron",
                "Personification",
                "Antithesis"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "84ca909fac8642caa7db915e5df323ad"
        },
        {
            "question": "The child is the father of man.",
            "description": "An epigram is a saying which excites, surprises or grabs attention.",
            "answers": [
                "Epigram",
                "Oxymoron",
                "Simile"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "59cd70f8de014d568ad0cbf1cccc2408"
        },
        {
            "question": "Fools rush in where angels fear to tread.",
            "description": "An epigram is a saying which excites, surprises or grabs attention.",
            "answers": [
                "Irony",
                "Epigram",
                "Alliteration"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e248c1d9e6fe45d386e8987baefcac6e"
        },
        {
            "question": "I desired my dust to be mingled with yours.",
            "description": "When a statement is made emphatic by overstatement it is called hyperbole.",
            "answers": [
                "Hyperbole",
                "Epigram",
                "Antithesis"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "0f6d966bc41a4e75bbe1660fe068d6c1"
        },
        {
            "question": "An ambassador is an honest man who lies abroad for the good of his country.",
            "description": "When there is more than one meaning in the same word, it is called pun.",
            "answers": [
                "Euphemism",
                "Pun",
                "Hyperbole"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "51ab5e9d8cf7435abf479c8dda5754a8"
        },
        {
            "question": "The soldier fights for glory and a shilling a day!",
            "description": "When the ideas are presented in a descending order, it is called anticlimax.",
            "answers": [
                "Climax",
                "Anticlimax",
                "Pun"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "929c9d8cdcb64fcd9f0b19885c7f482f"
        }
    ]
}